Guide to the Historical Register of Yale University Data Cards
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Historical Register of Yale University data cards
1960-1995
RU 283
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27.25
The records consist of index cards, Yale Corporation meeting minutes, and lists documenting the professional careers of Yale's faculty, officers, and fellows for the Historical Register of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of index cards, Yale Corporation meeting minutes, and lists documenting the professional careers of Yale's faculty, officers, and fellows for the Historical Register of Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Historical register of Yale University; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Faculty information used in compiling the "Historical Register of Yale University", 1960-1995; Accession 1996-A-085
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Editing problems (Box 1)
  - New Entries for Volume 4 (in database)
    - A-C (Box 2)
    - D-G (Box 3)
    - H-L (Box 4)
    - M-R (Box 5)
    - S (Box 6)
    - T-Z (Box 7)
  - Updated entries for Volume 4 (in database). In Volume 3, additional information
    - Aaboe- Goldenberg (Box 8)
    - Goldenring- Nyfenger (Box 9)
    - O'Connor - Zweig (Box 10)
  - Entries to be omitted from Volume 4 and not entered in database
    - Problem box (Box 11)
    - Not entered "missing data" (Box 12)
    - New -not added marked omit? (Box 13)
    - Not entered - need to be checked (Box 14)
    - Not entered -need to be checked (Box 15)
    - Not entered - all medical? (Box 16)
    - Omit? (Box 17)
    - Not entered -Fellows (Box 18)
    - Not entered? (Box 19)
- Yale Corporation meeting minutes and lists used to compile the "Historical Register of Yale University", 1969-1982; Accession 1997-A-056
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Yale University Corporation meeting minutes
    - 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 10)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11 - 27)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28 - 36)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 37 - 45)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 46 - 52)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 53 - 58)
  - Residential College Fellows (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Office of the Secretary Lectureships, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 60)